Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 1: Stations, undated, 1858-1997
      - Monroe's, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 988)
      - Montague, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 989)
      - Montello, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 990)
      - Montello, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 10:, Folder 991)
      - Monument Beach, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 992)
      - Monument Beach, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1968 (Box 10:, Folder 993)
      - Morgan's, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 994)
      - Morgan's Crossing, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 995)
      - Morrills, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 996)
      - Mount Auburn, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 997)
      - Mount Bowdoin, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 998)
      - Mount Hope, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 999)
      - Mount Tom, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1000)
      - Myricks, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1001)
      - Myricks, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1906 (Box 10:, Folder 1002)
      - Myricks, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1959 (Box 10:, Folder 1003)
      - Myricks, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1928 (Box 10:, Folder 1004)
      - Nantucket Junction, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1005)
      - Natick, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1006)
      - Naukeag, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1007)
      - Needham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1009)
      - Needham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 10:, Folder 1010)
      - Needham Heights, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1959 (Box 10:, Folder 1011)
      - Needham Heights, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1959 (Box 10:, Folder 1012)
      - Needham Heights, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 10:, Folder 1013)
      - Needham Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1951 (Box 10:, Folder 1014)
      - Needham Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1963 (Box 10:, Folder 1015)
      - Needham Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 1016)
      - Needham Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 1017)
      - Needham Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 1018)
      - Nescham, Massachusetts, Massachusetts Bay Transportation Railroad station, 1986 (Box 10:, Folder 1019)
      - New Bedford, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1020)
      - New Lenox, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1022)
      - New Salem, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 1023)
      - New Salem, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 1024)
      - Newburyport, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1966 (Box 10:, Folder 1008)
      - Newell, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1021)
      - Newton Center, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 1025)
      - Newton Center, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 1026)
      - Newton Center, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 1027)
      - Newton Center, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 10:, Folder 1028)
      - Newton Heights, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1029)
      - Newton Lower Falls, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 10:, Folder 1030)
      - Newton Lower Falls, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1031)
      - Newton Upper Falls, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1961 (Box 10:, Folder 1032)
      - Newton Upper Falls, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1933 (Box 10:, Folder 1033)
      - Newton Upper Falls, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 1034)
      - Newton Upper Falls, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 1035)
      - Newton Upper Falls, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 1036)
      - Newton Upper Falls, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 1037)
      - Newtonville Yard Tower, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1949 (Box 10:, Folder 1038)
      - Norfolk, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1039)
      - Norfolk Downs, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1957 (Box 10:, Folder 1040)
      - Norfolk Downs, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1936 (Box 10:, Folder 1041)
      - Norfolk Downs, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1042)
      - North Abington, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1043)
      - North Abington, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1044)
      - North Abington, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1962 (Box 10:, Folder 1045)
      - North Abington, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1926 (Box 10:, Folder 1046)
      - North Acton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1047)
      - North Adams, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 1048)
      - North Adams, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 10:, Folder 1049)
      - North Attleboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1910 (Box 10:, Folder 1050)
      - North Attleboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 10:, Folder 1051)
      - North Attleboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1052)
      - North Bellingham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1937 (Box 10:, Folder 1053)
      - North Bellingham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1926 (Box 10:, Folder 1054)
      - North Billerica, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 10:, Folder 1055)
      - North Brookfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, cirac 1933 (Box 11:, Folder 1058)
      - North Brookfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1932 (Box 11:, Folder 1059)
      - North Brookfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1060)
      - North Chelmsford, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1061)
      - North Cohasset, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1062)
      - North Dana, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1064)
      - North Dighton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1065)
      - North Eastham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1066)
      - North Easton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1067)
      - North Easton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1068)
      - North Falmouth, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, 1968 (Box 11:, Folder 1069)
      - North Falmouth, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1070)
      - North Falmouth, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1968 (Box 11:, Folder 1071)
      - North Falmouth, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1968 (Box 11:, Folder 1072)
      - North Grafton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1073)
      - North Grafton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1939 (Box 11:, Folder 1074)
      - North Grafton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1075)
      - North Grafton, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1076)
      - North Hanson, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 11:, Folder 1083)
      - North Hatfield, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1084)
      - North Leominster, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1085)
      - North Lexington, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1086)
      - North Lexington, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1968 (Box 11:, Folder 1087)
      - North Littleton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1088)
      - North Oxford, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1089)
      - North Oxford Mills, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 11:, Folder 1090)
      - North Oxford Mills, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1091)
      - North Oxford Mills, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1092)
      - North Pepperell, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1093)
      - North Reading, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1094)
      - North Reading, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1095)
      - North Scituate, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1966 (Box 11:, Folder 1096)
      - North Scituate, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1097)
      - North Truro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1098)
      - North Westport, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1099)
      - North Weymouth, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1100)
      - North Willbraham, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1101)
      - North Wilbraham, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1102)
      - North Woburn, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1103)
      - North Woburn, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 11:, Folder 1104)
      - Northampton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1949 (Box 11:, Folder 1077)
      - Northampton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1919 (Box 11:, Folder 1078)
      - Northampton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1971 (Box 11:, Folder 1079)
      - Northampton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1983 (Box 11:, Folder 1080)
      - Northampton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1983 (Box 11:, Folder 1081)
      - Northampton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1983 (Box 11:, Folder 1082)
      - Northboro, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 10:, Folder 1056)
      - Northbridge, Massachusetts, railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1057)
      - Norwood, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1105)
      - Norwood, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1106)
      - Norwood, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1939 (Box 11:, Folder 1107)
      - Norwood Central, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1108)
      - Norwood Central, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1950 (Box 11:, Folder 1109)
      - Oakdale, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, circa 1910 (Box 11:, Folder 1110)
      - Oak Street, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 11:, Folder 1111)
      - Oak Street, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 11:, Folder 1112)
      - Old Furnace, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 11:, Folder 1113)
      - Old Furnace, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1114)
      - Onset, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1115)
      - Oxford, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1116)
      - Oxford, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1117)
      - Oxford, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1118)
      - Palmer, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1119)
      - Palmer, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 11:, Folder 1120)
      - Palmer, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1977 (Box 11:, Folder 1121)
      - Palmer, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1983 (Box 11:, Folder 1122)
      - Palmer, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1983 (Box 11:, Folder 1123)
      - Peabody, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1908 (Box 11:, Folder 1124)
      - Peabody, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1125)
      - Perry's, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1126)
      - Phillips Beach, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1127)
      - Pittsfield, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, 1963 (Box 11:, Folder 1128)
      - Plainville, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1129)
      - Plainville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1130)
      - Pleasant Hills, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1131)
      - Plimptonville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1929 (Box 11:, Folder 1132)
      - Plymouth, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1133)
      - Plympton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1936 (Box 11:, Folder 1134)
      - Plympton, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 11:, Folder 1135)
      - Pocasset, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1912 (Box 11:, Folder 1136)
      - Pocasset, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1137)
      - Pocasset, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1138)
      - Pocasset, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1139)
      - Pocasset, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1140)
      - Pocasset, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 11:, Folder 1141)
      - Pondville, Massachusetts, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1142)
      - Princeton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1143)
      - Provincetown, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1962 (Box 11:, Folder 1144)
      - Provincetown, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1145)
      - Quincy, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1146)
      - Quincy Adams, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1147)
      - Quincy Adams, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1148)
      - Quincy Adams, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 11:, Folder 1149)
      - Quinebaug, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 11:, Folder 1150)
      - Raddins, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1151)
      - Raddins, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1152)
      - Randolph, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1153)
      - Randolph, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1154)
      - Randolph Holbrook, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1155)
      - Raynham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1156)
      - Raynham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1936 (Box 11:, Folder 1157)
      - Reading, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1158)
      - Reading Highlands, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1159)
      - Red Bridge, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1160)
      - Red Bridge, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1161)
      - Red School, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1162)
      - Revere, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1163)
      - Richmond, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 11:, Folder 1164)
      - Richmond, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1965 (Box 11:, Folder 1165)
      - Richmond Furnace, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1932 (Box 11:, Folder 1166)
      - Richmond Summit, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1934 (Box 12:, Folder 1167)
      - Riverside, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1168)
      - Riverside, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1898 (Box 12:, Folder 1169)
      - Riverside, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1937 (Box 12:, Folder 1170)
      - Riverside, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1171)
      - River Street, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1965 (Box 12:, Folder 1172)
      - River Street, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 12:, Folder 1173)
      - Riverview, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1174)
      - Roberts, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1175)
      - Rochdale, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 12:, Folder 1176)
      - Rock, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1177)
      - Rock, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1931 (Box 12:, Folder 1178)
      - Rockland, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1179)
      - Rocky Hill, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1180)
      - Rocky Hill, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1949 (Box 12:, Folder 1181)
      - Rowley, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1966 (Box 12:, Folder 1182)
      - Roxbury Crossing, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1183)
      - Russell, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1184)
      - Russell, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1185)
      - Rutland, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 12:, Folder 1186)
      - Sagamore, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1187)
      - Salem, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1188)
      - Sandwich, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1189)
      - Sandersdale, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 12:, Folder 1190)
      - Saugus, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1191)
      - Saugus, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1192)
      - Saugus, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1193)
      - Saundersville, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 12:, Folder 1194)
      - Saxonville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1195)
      - Saxonville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1933 (Box 12:, Folder 1196)
      - Saxonville, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1963 (Box 12:, Folder 1197)
      - Sharon, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1198)
      - Sharon, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 12:, Folder 1199)
      - Sharon, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 12:, Folder 1200)
      - Sharon, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1910 (Box 12:, Folder 1201)
      - Sharon Heights, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1938 (Box 12:, Folder 1202)
      - Sharon Heights, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1203)
      - Shawsheen Village, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1204)
      - Shelburne Falls, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1205)
      - Sherborn, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1929 (Box 12:, Folder 1206)
      - Sherborn, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, circa 1920 (Box 12:, Folder 1207)
      - Shirley Hills, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1208)
      - Silver Lake, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1209)
      - Smiths, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 12:, Folder 1210)
      - Smiths, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1935 (Box 12:, Folder 1211)
      - Smoth's Ferry, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1212)
      - Soapstone, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1213)
      - Soldiers Home, Massachusetts, Augusta, Winthrop & Gardiner Street Railroad station, 1907 (Box 12:, Folder 1214)
      - Somerset, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1930 (Box 12:, Folder 1215)
      - Somerset Junction, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1911 (Box 12:, Folder 1216)
      - Somerville, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1217)
      - Somerville Junction, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1218)
      - South Acton, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1962 (Box 12:, Folder 1219)
      - South Athol, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1220)
      - South Athol, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1221)
      - South Athol, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1934 (Box 12:, Folder 1222)
      - South Barre, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, circa 1930 (Box 12:, Folder 1223)
      - South Barre, Massachusetts, Boston & Albany Railroad station, 1934 (Box 12:, Folder 1224)
      - South Billerica, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1225)
      - South Billerica, Massachusetts, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1226)
      - South Braintree, Massachusetts, railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1228)
      - South Braintree, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1229)
      - South Bridgewater, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1934 (Box 12:, Folder 1234)
      - South Bridgewater, Massachusetts, Old Colony Railroad station, undated (Box 12:, Folder 1235)
      - South Chatham, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1937 (Box 12:, Folder 1236)
      - South Chelmsford, Massachusetts, New Haven Railroad station, 1937 (Box 12:, Folder 1237)